(Intro)
I saw you dancing in a crowded room
You look so happy when
I'm not with you
But then you saw me, caught
you by surprise
A single teardrop falling
from your eye
I don't know why I run away
I'll make you cry when I run away
You could've asked me why
I broke your heart
You could've told me
that you fell apart
But you walked past me
like I wasn't there
And just pretended like
you didn't care
I don't know why I run away
I'll make you cry when I run away
Take me back 'cause I wanna stay
Save your tears for another
Save your tears for another day
So, I made you think that
I would always stay
I said some things that
I should never say
Yeah, I broke your heart like
someone did to mine
And now you won't love
me for a second time
I don't know why I run away, oh, girl
Said I make you cry when I run away
Girl, take me back 'cause I wanna stay
Save your tears for another
I realize that I'm much too late
And you deserve someone better
Save your tears for another
day (Ooh, yeah)
Save your tears for another day (Yeah)
I don't know why I run away
I'll make you cry when I run away
Save your tears for another
day, ooh, girl (Ah)
I said save your tears
for another day (Ah)
Save your tears for another day (Ah)
by DPSoftware Foundation